

Samuel Ayomide Pitan

Web Developer | Junior Mobile Developer

(1) Ib Makarius Street, Ajah, Lagos

☑ pitan.samuel4@gmail.com

C +234 812 4633050

SOCIAL

in Samuel Ayomide Pitan

₩ iam3rillz

f Sam Ayomide Pitan

PROFILE

I am a self-motivated, diligent, and hard-working developer with an engineering mind and creativity is my passion. I possess strong communication skills and the ability to multi-task, which has allowed me to develop polished technical skills in a wide variety of areas.

I have experience working as both a freelance contractor and for a startup as a front-end developer.

SKILLS

- Html
- React Native
- Css
- React
- JavaScript
- WordPress

INTERESTS

₹ ⋒ Travel Gaming Reading

EDUCATION

React Native

Zero to Mastery Academy, Udemy 2022 - Present

) JavaScrip

Fatech Academy, Lagos, Nigeria

2022

Post Graduate Diploma in Digital Marketing

Chartered Institute of Social Media and Digital Marketing 2021

B.sc Computer Engineering

Olabisi Onabanjo University, Ogun State, Nigeria 2014 - 2019

EXPERIENCE

Fatech Academy | Front-End Developer and Instructor

2021 - PRESENT | https://fatech.ng

Working as a Front-End developer and instructor at Fatech Academy. Primary responsibilities are to develop the Front-End of Websites and also teach students who are willing to drift into the web design and development career.

Free Hosting Resell | Front-End Developer

2021 - PRESENT | https://freehostingresell.com

Free Hosting Resell offer free reselling platform for resellers to provide hosting services. My duties are to develop different responsive Front-End designs for Resellers' Websites

FHBRS | Front-End Developer

2021 - 2022 | https://fhbrs.com

I worked as a Front-End Developer at FHBRS, FHBRS is a platform where online digital businesses like Web Hosting, SMS, SMM and SEO Businesses, etc. offer a simple and easy reselling model for users.

CERTIFICATES

Associate Member - Chartered Institute of Social Media and Digital Marketing

We Presented the idea of a Forest fire prevention system using WSN.

LANGUAGES

• English

• Yoruba